{"question":"107 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"535","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"459","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"171 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"684","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"141 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"987","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"139 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"556","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"41 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"328","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"140 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"980","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"828","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"837","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"271 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"813","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"195 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"390","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"212 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"848","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"94 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"752","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"129 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"774","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"124 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"992","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"608","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"112 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"560","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"819","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"277 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"831","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"963","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"729","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"350","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"134 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"938","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"423 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"846","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"735","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"220 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"880","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"172 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"688","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"144 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"720","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"162 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"972","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"954","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"184 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"552","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"156 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"780","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"318 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"636","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"197 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"394","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"223 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"892","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"132 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"396","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"828","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"837","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"702","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"89 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"534","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"212 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"424","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"181 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"362","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"298 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"894","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"360","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"855","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"132 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"792","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"776","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"94 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"376","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"249 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"747","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"784","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"415","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"648","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"805","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"800","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"89 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"712","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"225 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"450","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"334 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"668","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"536","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"111 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"444","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"182 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"546","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"399 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"798","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"468","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"376","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"143 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"715","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"127 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"889","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"222 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"888","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"183 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"366","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"220 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"880","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"749","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"536","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"427 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"854","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"156 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"936","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"690","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"346 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"692","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"293 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"879","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"247 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"494","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"672","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"405","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"531","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"139 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"556","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"378 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"756","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"336","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"294 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"882","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"111 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"333","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"324","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"450","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"714","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"657","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"119 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"714","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"490 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"980","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"459","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"558","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"630","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"432","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"327 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"654","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"441","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"175 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"525","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"429 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"858","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"609","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"154 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"770","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"82 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"328","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"616","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"412 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"824","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"457 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"914","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"497 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"994","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"253 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"759","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"664","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"140 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"980","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"163 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"815","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"756","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"616","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"400","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"400","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"856","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"137 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"548","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"141 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"987","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"325 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"975","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"273 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"819","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"162 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"324","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"198 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"396","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"150 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"600","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"675","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"291 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"873","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"352","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"89 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"801","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"552","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"220 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"880","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"774","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"155 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"775","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"127 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"762","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"450","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"161 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"805","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"301 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"602","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"121 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"968","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"114 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"342","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"406","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"398 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"796","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"114 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"342","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"704","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"143 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"715","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"270 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"810","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"405","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"189 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"945","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"144 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"864","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"159 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"636","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"171 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"684","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"267 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"534","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"173 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"865","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"259 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"518","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"218 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"654","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"89 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"356","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"113 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"678","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"211 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"422","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"191 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"955","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"118 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"826","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"201 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"804","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"384","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"462","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"308","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"121 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"605","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"136 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"952","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"576","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"464","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"382 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"764","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"135 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"810","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"145 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"725","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"168 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"504","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"225 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"900","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"936","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"143 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"715","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"178 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"712","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"376","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"151 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"604","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"570","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"324 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"648","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"594","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"322 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"644","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"145 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"725","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"224 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"896","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"560","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"747","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"278 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"834","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"358 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"716","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"455","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"651","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"133 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"798","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"154 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"462","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"120 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"960","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"138 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"966","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"618","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"467 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"934","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"46 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"322","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"122 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"732","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"600","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"981","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"316","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"406","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"194 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"970","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"405","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"271 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"542","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"339 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"678","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"168 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"840","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"516","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"480","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"420","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"511","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"546","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"147 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"588","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"675","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"568","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"688","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"240 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"480","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"140 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"560","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"567","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"882","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"632","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"585","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"150 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"450","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"450","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"154 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"924","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"123 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"492","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"38 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"342","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"321 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"963","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"765","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"436 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"872","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"963","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"139 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"834","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"432","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"82 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"410","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"690","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"130 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"390","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"183 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"366","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"472","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"222 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"888","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"728","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"227 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"908","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"792","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"249 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"747","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"174 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"522","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"141 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"423","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"504","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"936","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"173 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"865","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"213 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"639","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"129 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"903","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"333","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"125 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"750","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"200 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"600","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"123 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"984","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"122 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"976","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"528","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"124 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"868","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"808","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"366 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"732","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"384","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"510","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"315","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"291 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"582","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"380","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"310","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"184 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"920","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"696","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"134 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"804","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"242 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"968","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"450","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"472 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"944","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"151 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"604","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"138 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"828","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"123 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"984","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"528","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"153 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"765","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"402 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"804","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"434","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"164 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"656","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"441","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"192 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"384","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"654","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"355","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"46 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"368","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"657","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"552","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"206 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"824","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"116 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"928","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"688","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"763","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"864","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"247 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"988","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"144 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"720","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"224 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"896","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"391 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"782","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"261 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"783","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"657","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"679","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"141 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"564","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"568","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"236 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"708","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"585","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"388","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"324","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"130 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"910","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"431 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"862","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"768","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"584","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"936","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"374 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"748","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"129 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"645","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"130 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"910","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"293 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"586","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"735","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"308 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"616","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"278 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"556","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"141 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"846","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"460","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"94 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"658","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"136 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"544","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"498","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"384","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"300 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"900","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"531","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"735","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"496","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"132 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"924","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"456 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"912","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"159 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"954","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"203 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"812","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"496","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"129 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"903","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"570","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"148 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"592","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"332 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"664","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"303","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"124 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"868","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"120 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"960","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"498","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"247 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"988","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"484 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"968","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"131 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"524","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"465 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"930","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"275 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"825","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"972","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"123 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"738","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"320","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"137 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"411","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"336","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"296","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"248 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"744","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"405","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"660","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"198 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"792","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"171 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"855","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"588","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"372","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"111 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"888","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"152 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"912","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"528","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"981","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"395","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"479 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"958","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"333","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"882","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"170 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"510","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"450","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"158 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"790","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"512","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"357","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"540","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"810","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"792","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"170 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"850","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"612","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"120 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"360","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"153 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"765","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"82 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"410","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"630","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"131 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"917","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"283 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"566","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"124 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"620","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"927","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"232 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"696","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"477 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"954","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"199 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"995","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"434","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"469","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"765","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"380","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"640","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"129 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"774","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"178 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"534","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"38 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"304","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"113 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"791","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"126 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"756","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"644","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"873","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"378","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"345","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"294","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"420","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"954","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"570","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"486","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"747","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"172 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"344","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"215 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"645","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"239 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"956","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"124 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"744","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"348","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"313 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"939","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"714","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"392","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"405","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"157 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"471","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"444","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"134 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"938","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"435","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"595","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"666","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"504","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"441","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"404 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"808","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"621","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"360","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"882","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"485","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"630","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"357","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"126 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"756","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"325","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"250 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"750","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"182 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"728","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"154 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"924","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"280 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"840","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"616","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"169 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"845","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"621","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"648","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"114 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"684","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"150 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"750","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"630","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"644","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"462","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"161 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"322","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"873","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"440","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"945","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"185 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"370","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"119 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"952","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"142 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"994","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"396","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"178 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"890","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"252 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"756","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"360 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"720","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"387 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"774","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"544","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"324 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"972","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"696","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"848","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"920","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"191 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"764","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"312","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"396","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"558","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"49 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"441","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"138 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"552","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"127 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"762","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"43 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"301","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"356 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"712","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"263 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"526","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"136 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"952","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"174 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"696","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"327 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"981","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"400","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"372","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"360","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"306","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"114 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"912","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"167 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"835","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"132 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"924","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"392","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"131 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"524","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"82 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"656","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"137 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"822","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"312","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"139 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"417","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"308","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"840","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"340","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"832","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"408","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"133 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"798","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"167 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"334","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"118 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"708","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"686","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"233 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"932","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"333 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"666","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"567","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"240 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"720","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"208 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"832","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"135 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"540","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"384","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"420","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"112 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"784","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"154 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"770","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"665","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"567","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"434","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"535","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"163 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"489","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"148 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"888","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"350","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"239 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"717","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"124 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"620","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"226 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"678","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"211 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"844","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"560","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"489 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"978","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"306","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"237 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"948","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"405","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"211 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"844","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"505","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"560","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"314 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"628","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"228 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"684","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"247 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"741","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"148 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"592","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"201 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"402","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"464","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"129 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"387","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"145 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"870","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"370 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"740","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"760","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"248 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"496","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"324","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"581","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"372","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"261 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"783","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"193 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"386","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"158 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"632","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"664","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"155 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"620","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"191 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"955","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"575","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"455","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"324","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"118 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"826","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"760","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"195 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"585","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"468","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"190 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"760","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"558","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"194 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"776","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"624","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"693","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"180 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"720","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"448","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"46 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"322","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"490","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"749","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"155 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"775","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"546","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"236 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"944","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"654","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"447 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"894","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"123 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"861","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"142 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"994","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"216 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"648","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"522","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"320","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"94 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"846","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"340","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"308 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"924","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"180 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"900","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"396","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"230 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"460","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"357","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"455","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"654","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"82 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"492","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"239 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"478","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"177 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"531","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"768","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"125 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"875","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"380","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"137 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"822","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"123 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"984","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"350","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"366 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"732","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"111 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"444","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"274 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"822","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"343 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"686","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"640","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"384","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"303","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"174 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"870","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"552","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"191 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"764","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"891","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"140 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"700","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"576","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"153 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"765","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"128 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"384","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"121 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"605","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"311 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"622","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"122 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"854","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"173 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"865","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"432","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"128 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"768","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"306","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"490","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"139 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"834","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"132 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"792","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"152 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"608","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"832","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"546","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"495","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"742","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"438","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"142 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"852","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"244 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"976","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"616","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"202 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"606","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"196 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"784","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"152 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"760","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"165 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"825","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"126 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"504","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"217 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"651","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"160 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"320","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"399","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"118 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"590","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"332 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"664","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"496","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"873","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"125 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"750","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"688","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"312","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"201 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"804","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"545","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"131 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"786","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"686","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"805","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"702","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"686","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"233 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"699","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"163 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"978","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"202 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"606","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"169 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"845","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"253 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"759","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"338 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"676","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"251 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"753","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"125 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"375","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"440","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"588","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"618","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"423","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"808","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"468","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"679","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"819","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"229 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"687","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"616","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"310 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"930","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"408 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"816","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"495","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"114 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"684","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"327 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"981","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"490","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"144 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"720","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"122 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"610","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"630","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"271 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"813","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"123 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"984","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"155 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"465","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"756","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"864","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"122 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"366","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"412 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"824","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"118 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"590","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"190 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"950","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"558","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"472","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"585","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"800","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"155 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"930","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"185 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"925","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"560","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"336","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"880","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"252 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"756","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"185 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"925","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"164 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"656","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"480","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"154 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"924","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"121 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"968","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"394 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"788","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"182 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"364","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"319 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"957","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"416","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"46 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"414","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"450","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"462","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"187 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"748","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"219 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"876","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"149 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"596","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"176 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"352","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"672","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"178 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"890","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"287 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"861","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"318","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"143 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"572","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"383 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"766","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"125 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"875","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"82 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"738","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"453 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"906","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"199 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"796","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"149 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"894","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"153 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"918","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"531","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"475 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"950","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"244 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"976","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"882","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"300","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"185 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"925","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"568","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"552","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"151 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"453","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"390","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"124 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"744","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"191 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"764","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"162 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"810","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"624","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"702","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"141 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"705","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"305 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"610","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"132 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"924","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"424 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"848","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"89 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"356","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"153 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"918","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"540","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"35 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"315","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"171 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"855","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"131 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"917","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"255 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"765","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"576","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"450","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"630","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"197 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"394","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"125 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"625","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"351","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"837","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"432","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"425 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"850","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"142 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"994","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"152 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"912","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"488","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"612","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"214 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"856","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"576","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"405 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"810","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"936","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"329","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"560","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"742","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"644","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"432","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"792","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"336","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"176 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"880","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"295 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"885","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"400","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"172 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"688","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"184 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"736","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"990","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"441","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"675","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"600","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"173 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"865","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"172 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"516","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"205 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"410","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"483","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"918","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"239 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"956","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"132 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"792","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"441","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"355 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"710","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"325 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"650","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"405","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"386 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"772","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"553","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"118 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"590","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"398 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"796","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"118 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"944","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"135 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"405","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"312","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"147 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"735","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"728","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"251 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"502","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"94 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"846","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"546","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"540","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"462","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"301 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"602","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"137 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"685","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"774","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"873","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"130 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"910","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"776","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"299 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"598","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"654","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"288 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"576","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"729","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"140 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"700","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"424","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"245 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"980","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"528","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"909","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"128 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"896","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"89 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"356","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"194 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"388","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"134 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"938","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"487 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"974","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"233 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"932","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"266 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"532","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"161 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"483","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"283 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"849","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"151 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"755","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"225 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"450","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"94 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"376","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"127 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"889","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"211 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"422","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"121 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"968","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"749","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"135 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"405","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"198 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"792","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"550","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"374 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"748","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"89 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"356","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"312 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"624","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"141 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"705","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"819","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"158 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"632","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"219 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"876","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"824","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"553","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"720","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"331 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"993","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"810","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"154 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"770","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"640","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"41 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"369","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"163 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"652","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"448","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"592","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"666","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"402","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"530","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"499 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"998","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"158 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"632","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"810","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"792","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"197 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"985","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"414","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"198 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"792","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"249 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"996","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"192 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"960","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"237 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"474","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"238 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"952","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"483 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"966","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"94 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"470","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"774","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"856","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"648","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"749","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"94 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"564","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"122 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"366","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"728","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"800","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"345","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"416","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"800","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"666","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"430","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"124 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"992","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"848","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"729","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"518","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"211 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"844","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"235 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"705","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"297 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"891","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"377 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"754","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"128 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"896","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"152 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"304","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"309","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"146 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"876","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"300","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"488","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"350","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"357","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"518","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"364","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"187 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"561","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"332 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"996","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"137 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"685","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"936","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"196 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"784","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"162 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"324","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"434","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"122 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"854","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"121 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"484","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"352 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"704","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"900","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"900","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"137 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"959","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"119 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"833","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"654","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"336","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"213 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"852","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"520","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"776","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"672","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"197 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"985","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"180 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"720","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"446 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"892","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"219 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"876","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"320","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"429 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"858","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"528","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"333","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"147 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"588","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"140 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"980","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"588","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"191 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"955","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"648","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"116 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"580","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"819","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"553","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"231 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"924","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"200 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"600","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"330","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"728","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"348","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"403 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"806","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"111 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"999","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"329 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"658","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"420","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"185 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"925","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"377 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"754","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"756","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"819","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"450","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"116 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"580","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"169 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"507","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"94 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"658","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"94 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"658","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"141 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"564","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"114 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"912","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"293 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"879","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"760","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"197 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"985","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"211 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"844","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"447 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"894","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"206 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"824","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"168 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"840","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"768","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"124 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"744","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"178 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"712","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"427","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"253 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"759","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"255 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"510","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"320","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"486","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"408","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"485","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"188 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"564","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"352","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"305 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"915","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"180 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"900","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"882","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"172 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"344","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"588","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"513","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"214 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"642","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"113 * 8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"904","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"131 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"917","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"522","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54 * 9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"486","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"191 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"764","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"138 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"690","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"128 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"512","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"243 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"972","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"313 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"939","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"192 * 5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"960","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"290 * 3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"870","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"141 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"987","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"161 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"644","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"181 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"724","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"467 * 2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"934","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"312","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"208 * 4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"832","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"112 * 7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"784","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 * 6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"306","hint":"Ответ?"}]}